hothaat.com 2015-03-26

# Hothaat.com: India's 1st Dropshipping Website: Ab Business Karega India: Start Your Own Online Business Today.

Our commitment to privacy

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available from our footer navigation that is found on every page of our website. When you register with Hothaat, we ask you for personal information. We use this information to process your orders, conduct account verifications, and to communicate with you about the status of your orders. We also use your email address to send you newsletters you are subscribed to during registration, as well as messages about Hothaat special offers, promotional announcements and consumer surveys. Occasionally, we send our customers special offers and promotional information via postal mail, using the shipping address provided. If you no longer want to receive the newsletters or other announcements simply unsubscribe by checking the unsubscribe links.

The information we collect

This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the Hothaat website. On some pages, you can order memberships, order products, make requests, and register to receive materials. The types of personal information collected at these pages are:

  * Name
  * Billing address
  * Email address
  * Phone number
  * Credit/debit card information

On some pages, you can submit information about other people. For example, if you order a product and want it drop shipped directly to your customer, you will need to submit their address. In this circumstance, the types of personal information collected are:

  * Name
  * Shipping address
  * Phone number
  * Email

Disclaimer - 

Hothaat will not disclose your personal information provided in connection with membership registration or purchases, except with your knowledge and consent as described in this Privacy Policy or as may be required by law, or to protect the rights or property of Hothaat.

Information submitted by you online (such as information about products you purchase from us, your name, address, email address) may be shared with companies with which we have a commercial relationship, including companies through which you reached Hothaat. For example, if you make a purchase with us because of a special offer made through another site acting as a distributor of our products, in that circumstance you will be considered their customer as well.

We will not, except as may be required by law, share with any other party your password or payment information. We may also share information about you (including name, email address, phone number, and postal address) to our marketing partners or other companies with whom we have a commercial relationship so they may contact you about information and services that we feel you would benefit from.

Changes to our privacy policy

We reserve the right to change this privacy policy from time to time by publishing the revised privacy policy on our website. Please check this privacy policy regularly for modifications and updates. If you continue to use this website or if you provide any personal information after we post changes to this privacy policy, this will deemed your conclusive acceptance of any such changes.

If you have any queries or concerns regarding our privacy policies, please email us at support@hothaat.com
